Many people associate their self-worth with their work.
很多人把自我价值和自己的工作联系在一起。
The more successful their career, the better they feel about themselves.
事业越成功，他们的自我感觉就越好。
Work-related self-esteem is therefore a worthy ideal to pursue with vigor, right?
因此，与工作相关的自尊是一个值得全力追求的理想，对吧？
Well, not always.
其实，并非总是如此。
According to recent research, in which psychologists interviewed 370 full-time workers over a period of three weeks, the reality is a little more complicated.
最近的一项研究中，心理学家在三周时间里访谈了370名全职员工；根据这项研究，实际情况要稍微复杂一些。
And it involves negative as well as positive consequences.
而且，这其中既涉及负面后果，也涉及正面后果。
It’s natural to be drawn towards pleasure and to step away from pain.
受快乐吸引、远离痛苦，是很自然的事。
In the workplace, if that pleasure comes from a triumph which swells their self-respect, people will try to repeat the accomplishment.
在职场上，如果这种快乐来自一次令自尊心大增的重大成功，人们就会努力再次取得这样的成就。
But repeating that accomplishment is often not realistic, which can lead to severe negative emotional consequences when it doesn’t reoccur.
但再次取得这样的成就往往并不现实；成就一旦没有再现，就可能在情绪上造成严重的负面后果。
This form of motivation is widely regarded as a negative type of motivation.
这种形式的动机被普遍视为一种消极的动机类型。
It can hinder other more positive motivation types, such as completing a task purely because it’s fulfilling or enjoyable.
它可能会阻碍其他更积极的动机类型，比如仅仅因为一项任务让人有成就感或令人愉快而去完成它。
What consumes the employee instead is a pressing need to feel mighty and sure of themselves.
转而占据员工全部心思的，是一种迫切的需要：要觉得自己强大有力、对自己有把握。
They then take on only tasks and objectives which serve that ego-driven need.
于是，他们只承担那些能满足这种受自尊心驱使的需求的任务和目标。
As a result, to avoid feelings of shame and worthlessness associated with failure, they extend themselves to such a degree that there’s a subsequent adverse effect on their well-being.
因此，为了避免伴随失败而来的羞耻感和无价值感，他们竭尽全力，以至于随后会对自己的身心健康产生不利影响。
This internal pressure to succeed at all costs demands a lot of effort.
这种不惜一切代价也要成功的内在压力，要求人付出大量努力。
It depletes their energy, culminating in disproportionate levels of damaging sentiment.
这种压力会耗尽他们的精力，最终导致他们产生过度强烈的有害情绪。
Those negative emotions mount into heightened anxiety, impacting their ability to make the most of their personal life.
这些负面情绪不断累积，变成更强烈的焦虑，影响他们充分享受个人生活的能力。
Their desire to avoid feeling inferior ends up making them feel inferior when it comes to their diminished capacity for friendship and leisure.
他们想避免低人一等的感觉，这种愿望最终却让他们因交友和享受闲暇的能力减退而觉得自己低人一等。
They end up dissatisfied both at work and outside of it.
最终，他们在工作中和工作之外都感到不满。
But thankfully, for those people compelled almost entirely by this specific form of motivation, the news isn’t all bad, or bad at all.
但值得庆幸的是，对于那些几乎完全受这种特定形式的动机驱使的人来说，这并不全是坏消息，或者说根本就算不上坏消息。
The study also discovered several positive outcomes that can actually outweigh the harmful ones.
这项研究还发现了几项积极的结果，它们实际上可能胜过有害的结果。
Though these types of employees are motivated by the desire to avoid negative consequences, they are also motivated by the excitement of pursuing emotional rewards.
这类员工虽然受到避免负面后果这一愿望的激励，但同样也受到追求情感回报时那种兴奋感的激励。
This excitement makes pursuing goals enjoyable and stimulates pleasure and pride that would result from success.
这种兴奋感让追求目标变得令人愉快，并激发出成功后会随之产生的快乐和自豪。
An effect of the positive motivation is that it neutralizes the effects of negative motivation.
积极动机的一个作用是抵消消极动机的影响。
Sure, it affects people’s personal lives to what could be deemed an unhealthy extent, because leisure activities are often seen as a part of life that must be sacrificed to manage work and family demands.
诚然，它对人们个人生活的影响，到了可以视为不健康的程度，因为人们常把休闲活动看作为了应付工作和家庭的需求而必须牺牲的那部分生活。
However, the way people feel about their work has less to do with whether they’re motivated by the preservation of self-esteem and more with the fact that they’re simply motivated.
然而，人们对工作的感受如何，与其说跟他们是否受维护自尊的驱动有关，不如说跟他们单纯有动力这一事实有关。